<ModMetaData>
	<name>Vanilla Races Expanded - Sanguophage</name>
	<author>Oskar Potocki, Sarg Bjornson, Erin</author>
	<supportedVersions>

		<li>1.4</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<modDependencies>
		<li>
			<packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
			<displayName>Harmony</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
		</li>
		<li>
			<packageId>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</packageId>
			<displayName>Vanilla Expanded Framework</displayName>
			<steamWorkshopUrl>https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2023507013</steamWorkshopUrl>
			<downloadUrl>https://github.com/Vanilla-Expanded/VanillaExpandedFramework</downloadUrl>
		</li>
	</modDependencies>
	<loadAfter>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
		<li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Biotech</li>
		<li>brrainz.harmony</li>
		<li>OskarPotocki.VanillaFactionsExpanded.Core</li>

	</loadAfter>

	<packageId>vanillaracesexpanded.sanguophage</packageId>
	<description>Introducing Vanilla Races Expanded - Sanguophage, a thrilling mod that adds a captivating layer of depth to the world of Rimworld. This expansive mod brings the ancient and terrifying power of vampiric bloodlines to life, infusing your gameplay with unique genes, incredible abilities, and unforgettable xenotypes. The Sanguophage mod offers an immersive experience, where players must navigate complex management of their sanguophages' hemogen needs and the captivating dynamics of different blood types. Brace yourself for blood moon events, the challenge of the hemohunter mental state, and master new deathrest building enhancements.

Summary of Features:

- Three New Xenotypes: Experience the Strigoi, Ekkimian, and Bruxa subxenotypes, each with their own distinct abilities, appearances, and playstyles. Forge a new path on the Rimworld with these powerful vampiric entities.

- Hemogen Management: Sanguophages require the lifeblood of their prey for sustenance. Balance their needs by acquiring blood packs, using prisoners, or employing diplomacy to obtain the precious hemogen they crave.

- Blood Types and Affinities: Discover the effects of different blood types and how they impact sanguophage abilities, social interactions, and compatibility. Master this dynamic to create an unstoppable vampire colony.

- Blood Moon Events: Prepare for the ominous Blood Moon, an event that strengthens sanguophages while presenting unique challenges and opportunities to expand your empire.

- Hemohunter Mental State: Tread carefully as your sanguophages can enter a frenzied state of bloodlust, hunting down prey in order to sate their unquenchable thirst.

- Deathrest Building Enhancements: Customize your sanguophages' lairs with new building options, providing comfort and safety for your vampires during their daily rest.

Unleash the darkness within and conquer the Rimworld with the power of the Sanguophage in Vanilla Races Expanded - Sanguophage. Are you ready to embrace your inner vampire?
</description>
</ModMetaData>
